Metrication Records, circa 1975-1987
Smithsonian Institution Archives
Metrication Records
circa 1975-1987
Smithsonian Institution Archives, Washington, D.C., osiaref@si.edu
Smithsonian Institution, Assistant Secretary for Administration
SI Records
1 cu. ft. (1 record storage box)
Accession 90-045
Descriptive Entry
This accession consists of correspondence, memoranda, questionnaires, minutes of meetings, metrication reports, a proposed worklist for the Interagency Committee on Metric Policy, news releases, U. S. Metric Board records, summary reports, and brochures. Materials also include agenda listings, American National Metric Council Conference records, a directory of attendees, metric measurement information, and state/regional status reports. Most of the records were created and maintained by John F. Jameson.
Index Terms
This collection is indexed under the following access terms. These are links to collections with related topics, persons or places.
Name
Jameson, John F.; United States Metric Board.; United States. Interagency Committee on Metric Policy.; United States. Metrication Operating Committee.
Subject
Metric system
Physical Characteristics of Materials in the Collection
Brochures; Clippings; Manuscripts; Drawings
- Box 1
  - Jane's 1986-1987 Metric (Box 1 of 1)
  - Metric (Box 1 of 1)
  - Metrification at the Smithsonian (Box 1 of 1)
  - Metric Questionnaire Responses - 1983 (Box 1 of 1)
  - MOC - Metric meeting (June 17, 1981) (Box 1 of 1)
  - Metrication Operating Committee - Meeting minutes and Notes (Box 1 of 1)
  - Metric Operating Committee (Box 1 of 1)
  - SI Conversion to Metric - Curators Questionnaire Response (Box 1 of 1)
  - Metric 1983 (Box 1 of 1)
  - U. S. Metric Association (Box 1 of 1)
  - Metric Conference - 1984 (Box 1 of 1)